If we're sending out all this data to human labelers,
如果我们将数据发送给人工标注者
is there something that can speed this process along with this Ground Truth feature?
有没有什么方面可以加快 Ground Truth 功能？
What comes to mind? What would help?
你想到了什么你觉得需要什么帮助？
Yeah. Well, I mean, ideally the process will be automated where you
嗯我认为 理想情况下 这个流程应该自动化
could maybe use some humans but use something like a Machine Learning Algorithm.
可以有人工介入 但是希望有个机器学习算法
Yeah. So that's exactly what we thought about as well.
是的这正是我们的想法
If you have images and within the images you want to identify birds,
假设需要识别图像中的某些对象
and I don't know dogs,
例如狗
and cats, and horses.
猫或马
If you have a 1,000 images,
如果有 1,000 个图像
and then out of the first 100 images if you have a good shuffling mechanism,
并且有很好的随机重排机制
then you stand opportunities to have all of
那么前 100 个图像就可能
these categories of animals that you want to recognize in the first 100 images.
包含你要识别的所有动物类别
So it would be very beneficial to identify these animals within the first 100 images,
所以最好能从前 100 个图像中识别这些动物
and let a Machine Learning model learn how to identify them in the future,
让机器学习模型能学习以后如何识别它们
and pass the 900 other images through the Machine Learning model first,
并将剩下的 900 个图像先放到机器学习模型里
and then see if it's capable of recognizing these animals on your behalf.
看看模型能否代替你识别这些动物
Of course, it's an ML model,
因为是机器学习模型
it's automated, it's fast.
所以是自动化的 速度很快
You don't need to go back to humans.
不需要再人工干预
If it's capable of getting that done,
如果能够识别
then it feeds that directly into your training dataset.
则将数据直接放到训练集中
If it's not capable of getting that done,
如果不能识别
or if it doesn't have a high confidence in having gotten that done correctly,
或者识别的置信水平不高
then it passes it back to the human annotators.
则再发给人工注释者
That's essentially what we built as part of Amazon SageMaker Ground Truth,
这正是 Amazon SageMaker Ground Truth 的功能
where besides the ability to send the data to
除了能够将数据发送给
people that would eventually label the data manually,
最终手动标记数据的人员之外
you can also create what we call an active learning model that would
还可以创建主动学习模型
try first to label the data after learning from the first batch,
在学习第一批数据后先尝试标记数据
and then if it is highly confident in its ability to label the dataset in the future,
如果对未来标记数据很有信心
pass that directly to the training data.
则将数据直接放入训练集中
If it's not, it'll pass it back to the human.
如果没有信心 则发给人工标注者
So what we see there is that there is
客户可以借助该功能
a 70 percent saving that our customers are having now.
节省 70% 的成本
Autodesk is an example of a customer that is using SageMaker Ground Truth to label
Autodesk 就是使用 SageMaker Ground Truth
their dataset and they are able to save
标记数据集的示例客户
70 percent cost and time just by
通过 Machine Learning Ground Truth 的自动化流程
automating the process with Machine Learning Ground Truth.
他们能够节省 70% 的成本和时间
Yeah. It's interesting when you save a confidence as well
嗯你提到的置信水平很有意思
because when you think of the case of medical images,
对于医学影像来说
the images presumably that would be sent back to
影像一般需要发送给人类标注者
human labelers would be like the most complicated or sort of strange example.
这属于最复杂、奇怪的示例
So it's also a way of servicing interesting images or whatever data points you have,
还包括有趣的图像或其他数据点
which I think has some implications for research outside of academia and that's great.
该工具对学术之外的研究也很有用 太棒了